Guide to the Stanford University Medical Experimental Computer Resource (SUMEX) Records SC1248
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University Medical Experimental Computer Resource (SUMEX) records
1975-1991
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC1248
300 Linear Feet
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Artificial intelligence -- History. -- California -- San Francisco Bay Area; Medical applications
- SUMEX-AIM (Stanford University Medical Experimental Computer for Artificial Intelligence in Medicine) TENEX computer files, 1974-1983; Accession ARCH-2007-156; 18739.2 megabyte(s) (246,431 files in 5,218 directories)
  Scope and Contents
  The SUMEX-AIM network was a nationally-shared computing resource devoted entirely to designing AI applications for the biomedical sciences. Headed by Ed Feigenbaum and Joshua Lederberg, it demonstrated the power of the ARPAnet for scientific collaboration.
  SUMEX-AIM was built using LISP (INTERLISP), one of the earliest high-level programming languages, which introduced many ideas such as garbage collection, recursive functions, symbolic expressions, and dynamic type-checking. INTERLISP was a programming environment built around a version of the Lisp programming language. Interlisp development began in 1967 at Bolt, Beranek and Newman in Cambridge, Massachusetts as BBN LISP, which ran on PDP-10 machines running the TENEX operating system. When Danny Bobrow, Warren Teitelman and Ronald Kaplan moved from BBN to Xerox PARC, it was renamed Interlisp. Interlisp became a popular Lisp development tool for AI researchers at Stanford University and elsewhere in the DARPA community. Interlisp was notable for the integration of interactive development tools into the environment, such as a debugger, an automatic correction tool for simple errors (DWIM - "do what I mean"), and analysis tools.
  Access to Collection
  The materials are restricted. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
- SUMEX Computer Tapes
  - Time: 800; Tape 1, 1977 Jan 30; 1.1 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Time: 800; Tape 2, 1977 Jan 30; 1.2 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Time: 800; Tape 3, 1977 Jan 30; 1.3 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Time: 800; Tape 4, 1977 Jan 30; 1.4 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Time: 800; Tape 5, 1977 Jan 30; 1.5 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Time: 800; Tape 6, 1977 Jan 30; 1.6 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Time: 800; Tape 7, 1977 Jan 30; 1.7 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - Time: 800; Tape 8, 1977 Jan 30; 1.8 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Time: 800; Tape 9, 1977 Jan 30; 1.9 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Time: 800; Tape 10, 1977 Jan 30; 1.10 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - Time: 800; Tape 11, 1977 Jan 30; 1.11 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Time: 800; Tape 12, 1977 Jan 30; 1.12 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - Time: 800; Tape 13, 1977 Jan 30; 2.1 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Time: 800; Tape 14, 1977 Jan 30; 2.2 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Time: 800; Tape 15, 1977 Jan 30; 2.3 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Time: 800; Tape 16, 1977 Jan 30; 2.4 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Time: 800; Tape 17, 1977 Jan 30; 2.5 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Time: 800; Tape 18, 1977 Jan 30; 2.6 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - Time: 800; Tape 19, 1977 Jan 30; 2.7 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - Time: 800; Tape 20, 1977 Jan 30; 2.8 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Time: 800; Tape 21, 1977 Jan 30; 2.9 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - Time: 800; Tape 22, 1977 Jan 30; 2.10 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Sequence 1; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 3.1 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Sequence 2; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 3.2 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Sequence 1; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 3.3 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Sequence 2; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 3.4 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Sequence 3; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 3.5 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - Sequence 4; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 3.6 (Box 3, Item 6)
  - Sequence 5; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 3.7 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - Sequence 6; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 3.8 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - Sequence 7; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 4.1 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - Sequence 8; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 4.2 (Box 4, Item 2)
  - Sequence 9; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 4.3 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - Sequence 10; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 4.4 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - Sequence 11; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 4.5 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - Sequence 12; Tape 1 of 222, 1980 Jan 27; 4.6 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - Sequence 4; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 4.7 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - Sequence 5; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 4.8 (Box 4, Item 8)
  - Sequence 6; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.1 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Sequence 7; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.2 (Box 5, Item 2)
  - Sequence 8; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.3 (Box 5, Item 3)
  - Sequence 9; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.4 (Box 5, Item 4)
  - Sequence 10; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.5 (Box 5, Item 5)
  - Sequence 11; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.6 (Box 5, Item 6)
  - Sequence 12; Tape 223, 1980 Jan 27; 5.7 (Box 5, Item 7)
  - 1-28, 1989; 6.1 (Box 6, Item 1)
  - 1-29, 1989; 6.2 (Box 6, Item 2)
  - 1-30, 1989; 6.3 (Box 6, Item 3)
  - 1-31, 1989; 6.4 (Box 6, Item 4)
  - 1-32, 1989; 6.5 (Box 6, Item 5)
  - 1-33, 1989; 6.6 (Box 6, Item 6)
  - 1-35; Tape 1 of 1 by DK, 1988 Dec 4; 6.7 (Box 6, Item 7)
  - 1-36; Tape 1 of 2 by DK, 1988 Dec 4; 6.8 (Box 6, Item 8)
  - 1-37, 6.9 (Box 6, Item 9)
  - 1-38, 7.1 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - 1-39, 7.2 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - 1-40, 7.3 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - 1-41; Tape 1 of 2 by WS, 1989 Feb 13; 7.4 (Box 7, Item 4)
  - 1-43, 7.5 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - 1-44, 7.6 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - 1-45; Tape 1 of 2 by WS, 1989 Feb 13; 7.7 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - 1-46, 7.8 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - 1-47; Tape 2 of 2 by RBT, 7.9 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - 1-48, 8.1 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - 1-49, 8.2 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - 1-50, 8.3 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - 3-7; Tape 1 of 1, 1988 May 22; 8.4 (Box 8, Item 4)
  - 3-8, 8.5 (Box 8, Item 5)
  - 3-10; Tape 2 of 4 by DK; 1st inode: 18469, 1988 Sept 13; 8.6 (Box 8, Item 6)
  - 3-11, 1988 Sept 13; 8.7 (Box 8, Item 7)
  - 3-12; Tape 4 of 4 by DK; 1st inode: 43037, 1988 Sept 13; 8.8 (Box 8, Item 8)
  - 3-13; Tape 1 of 4 by DK, 1988 Sept 13; 8.9 (Box 8, Item 9)
  - 3-14, 1988 Sept 13; 9.1 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - 3-15; Tape 3 of 4 by DK; 1st inode: 20876, 1988 Sept 13; 9.2 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - 3-16, 9.3 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - 3-17; Tape 1 of 1 by DK, 1988 Apr 17; 9.4 (Box 9, Item 4)
  - 3-18, 9.5 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - 3-19, 9.6 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - 3-20; Tape 3 of 5 by DK; 1st inode: 26919, 1988 Apr 17; 9.7 (Box 9, Item 7)
  - 3-21; Tape 4 of 5 by DK; 1st inode: 36092, 1988 Apr 17; 9.8 (Box 9, Item 8)
  - 3-22; Tape 5 of 5 by DK; 1st inode: 47393, 1988 Apr 17; 9.9 (Box 9, Item 9)
  - 3-23; Tape 1 of 1, 1988 Apr 17; 10.1 (Box 10, Item 1)
  - 3-24, 10.2 (Box 10, Item 2)
  - 3-25, 10.3 (Box 10, Item 3)
  - 1 19 Dg; Tape 2 of 3 by VH; 1st inode: 47373, 1991 Jan 20; 10.4 (Box 10, Item 4)
  - 1 20 Dg, 1990 Dec 9; 10.5 (Box 10, Item 5)
  - 3-34, 10.6 (Box 10, Item 6)
  - Blue 2 4-7, 1991 May 8; 10.7 (Box 10, Item 7)
  - Blue 2 4-8; D2, 1991 May 8; 10.8 (Box 10, Item 8)
  - Blue 2 4-9; Tape 3 of 3, 1991 May 8; 10.9 (Box 10, Item 9)
  - Blue 2 4-10, 1991 Sept 5; 11.1 (Box 11, Item 1)
  - Blue 2 4-11; Tape 2 of 3 by VH, 1991 Aug 1; 11.2 (Box 11, Item 2)
  - Blue 2 4-12; Tape 3 of 3 by VH, 11.3 (Box 11, Item 3)
  - Blue 2 4-13; Level 9 by mtm, 1991 Aug 2; 11.4 (Box 11, Item 4)
  - Blue 2 4-14; Tape 2 of 3 by VH, 1991 Aug 2; 11.5 (Box 11, Item 5)
  - [Blue 2 4-15]; Tape 3 of 3 by VH, 1991 Aug 2; 11.6 (Box 11, Item 6)
  - [Blue 2 4-16]; Tape 1 of 3 by VH, 11.7 (Box 11, Item 7)
  - Blue 2 4-17, 11.8 (Box 11, Item 8)
  - Blue 2 4-18, 11.9 (Box 11, Item 9)
  - Blue 2 4-19; Tape 1 of 3 by VH, 1991 Jun 11; 12.1 (Box 12, Item 1)
  - Blue 2 4-20, 1991 Sept 10; 12.2 (Box 12, Item 2)
  - Blue 2 4-21; Tape 3 of 3 by VH, 1991 Jul 9; 12.3 (Box 12, Item 3)
  - Blue 2 4-22, 12.4 (Box 12, Item 4)
  - Blue 2 4-23; Tape 2 of 3 by VH, 1991 Aug 7; 12.5 (Box 12, Item 5)
  - Blue 2 4-24; Tape 3 of 3 by VH, 1991 Aug 7; 12.6 (Box 12, Item 6)
  - Blue 2 4-25, 1991 Sept 15; 12.7 (Box 12, Item 7)
  - Blue 2 4-26, 1991 Sept 15; 12.8 (Box 12, Item 8)
  - Blue 2 4-27, 1991 Aug 15; 12.9 (Box 12, Item 9)
  - Blue 2 4-34, 13.1 (Box 13, Item 1)
  - Blue 2 4-35, 13.2 (Box 13, Item 2)
  - Unlabeled, 13.3 (Box 13, Item 3)
  - 2-1; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Apr 21; 13.4 (Box 13, Item 4)
  - 2-2; Tape 2 of 2 by VH, 1991 Apr 21; 13.5 (Box 13, Item 5)
  - 2-3; Tape 2 of 2 by VH, 13.6 (Box 13, Item 6)
  - 2-4; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Apr 21; 13.7 (Box 13, Item 7)
  - 2-5, 13.8 (Box 13, Item 8)
  - 2-6, 13.9 (Box 13, Item 9)
  - 2-7, 14.1 (Box 14, Item 1)
  - 2-8; Tape 3 of 6 by VH; 1st inode: 86099, 1991 Apr 21; 14.2 (Box 14, Item 2)
  - 2-9; Tape 4 of 6 by VH; 1st inode: 125089, 1991 Apr 21; 14.3 (Box 14, Item 3)
  - 2-10; Tape 5 of 6 by VH; 1st inode: 168218, 1991 Apr 21; 14.4 (Box 14, Item 4)
  - 2-11; Tape 6 of 6 by VH; 1st inode: 209190, 1991 Apr 21; 14.5 (Box 14, Item 5)
  - 2-12, 14.6 (Box 14, Item 6)
  - 2-13, 14.7 (Box 14, Item 7)
  - 2-14; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Apr 21; 14.8 (Box 14, Item 8)
  - 2-15, 14.9 (Box 14, Item 9)
  - 2 1 Dg, 15.1 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - 2 4 Dg, 15.2 (Box 15, Item 2)
  - 2 5 Dg; Tape 2 of 2 by VH; 1st inode: 41234, 1991 Jul 21; 15.3 (Box 15, Item 3)
  - 2 7 Dg, 15.4 (Box 15, Item 4)
  - 2 8 Dg; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Jul 21; 15.5 (Box 15, Item 5)
  - 2 10 Dg, 15.6 (Box 15, Item 6)
  - 5 19 Dg, 15.7 (Box 15, Item 7)
  - 5 20 Dg, 15.8 (Box 15, Item 8)
  - 1-17, 15.9 (Box 15, Item 9)
  - 1-18, 16.1 (Box 16, Item 1)
  - 1-19, 16.2 (Box 16, Item 2)
  - 1-20, 16.3 (Box 16, Item 3)
  - 1-21, 16.4 (Box 16, Item 4)
  - 1-22, 16.5 (Box 16, Item 5)
  - 1-23, 16.6 (Box 16, Item 6)
  - 1-24, 16.7 (Box 16, Item 7)
  - 1-25, 16.8 (Box 16, Item 8)
  - 2-26, 16.9 (Box 16, Item 9)
  - 2-27; Tape 2 of 2 by VH; 1st inode: 51219, 1991 Feb 18; 17.1 (Box 17, Item 1)
  - 2-28, 1991 Feb 18; 17.2 (Box 17, Item 2)
  - 2-29; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Feb 18; 17.3 (Box 17, Item 3)
  - 2-30; Tape 2 of 2 by KM; 1st inode: 11070, 1991 Feb 18; 17.4 (Box 17, Item 4)
  - 2-32, 17.5 (Box 17, Item 5)
  - 2-33; Tape 4 of 6 by VH; 1st inode: 124949, 1991 Feb 18; 17.6 (Box 17, Item 6)
  - 2-34, 17.7 (Box 17, Item 7)
  - 2-35, 17.8 (Box 17, Item 8)
  - 2-38, 17.9 (Box 17, Item 9)
  - 2-39, 18.1 (Box 18, Item 1)
  - 2-40; Tape 2 of 3 by VH; 1st inode: 47495, 1991 Jan 6; 18.2 (Box 18, Item 2)
  - 2-41; Tape 3 of 3 by VH; 1st inode: 96562, 1991 Jan 6; 18.3 (Box 18, Item 3)
  - 2-42; Tape 1 of 2 by VH, 1991 Feb 18; 18.4 (Box 18, Item 4)
  - 2-43; Tape 2 of 2 by VH, 1991 Feb 18; 18.5 (Box 18, Item 5)
  - Blue 4 1-2; lusr #1, 1988 Oct 30; 18.6 (Box 18, Item 6)
  - Blue 4 1-3; lusr #2, 1988 Oct 30; 18.7 (Box 18, Item 7)
  - Blue 4 1-4; lusr #3, 1988 Oct 30; 18.8 (Box 18, Item 8)
  - Blue 4 1-5, 18.9 (Box 18, Item 9)
  - Blue 4 1-6; la #2, 1988 Oct 30; 19.1 (Box 19, Item 1)
  - Blue 4 1-7; la #3; Tape 3 of 5 by DK; 1st inode: 18442, 1988 Oct 30; 19.2 (Box 19, Item 2)
  - Blue 4 1-8; la #4, 1988 Oct 30; 19.3 (Box 19, Item 3)
  - Blue 4 1-9; Tape 5 of 5 by DK; 1st inode: 51474, 1988 Oct 30; 19.4 (Box 19, Item 4)
  - Blue 4 1-10; lb #1, 1988 Oct 30; 19.5 (Box 19, Item 5)
  - [Blue 4 1-11]; lb #2, 1988 Oct 30; 19.6 (Box 19, Item 6)
  - Blue 4 1-12, 19.7 (Box 19, Item 7)
  - Blue 1-13; lb #3, 19.8 (Box 19, Item 8)
  - Archive 318, 1977 DEc 11; 20.1 (Box 20, Item 1)
  - Archive 320; Tape 1 of 1, 1977 Dec 18; 20.2 (Box 20, Item 2)
  - Archive 322; Time: 2300, 1977 Dec 27; 20.3 (Box 20, Item 3)
  - Archive 324; Tape 1 of 1, 1978 Jan 6; 20.4 (Box 20, Item 4)
  - Archive 326, 1978 Jan; 20.5 (Box 20, Item 5)
  - Archive 328, 1978 Jun 27; 20.6 (Box 20, Item 6)
  - Archive 330, 20.7 (Box 20, Item 7)
  - Archive 332, 20.8 (Box 20, Item 8)
  - Archive 334; Tape 1 of 1, 1978 Feb 21; 20.9 (Box 20, Item 9)
  - Archive 336, 1978 Mar 1; 21.1 (Box 21, Item 1)
  - Archive 338, 21.2 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - 1-25; Tape 2 of 5 by AJ; 1st inode: 12560, 1986 Sept 24; 21.3 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - 1-26; Tape 3 of 5 by AJ; 1st inode: 26877, 1986 Sept 24; 21.4 (Box 21, Item 4)
  - 1-27; Tape 4 of 5 by AJ; 1st inode: 36871, 1986 Sept 24; 21.5 (Box 21, Item 5)
  - 1-28; Tape 5 of 5; 1st inode: 49229, 1986 Sept 24; 21.6 (Box 21, Item 6)
  - 1-29, 21.7 (Box 21, Item 7)
  - 1-30, 21.8 (Box 21, Item 8)
  - 1-31, 21.9 (Box 21, Item 9)
  - 1-32, 22.1 (Box 22, Item 1)
  - 1-33, 22.2 (Box 22, Item 2)
  - 1-34; la #2, 22.3 (Box 22, Item 3)
  - 1-35, 22.4 (Box 22, Item 4)
  - 4-9; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 14; 22.5 (Box 22, Item 5)
  - 4-10; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 14; 22.6 (Box 22, Item 6)
  - 4-11; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 14; 22.7 (Box 22, Item 7)
  - 4-12; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 20; 22.8 (Box 22, Item 8)
  - 4-13; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 20; 22.9 (Box 22, Item 9)
  - 4-14; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 20; 23.1 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - 4-15; Tape 1 of 1 by DW, 1986 Aug 20; 23.2 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - 4-16; Tape 1 of 1 by AJ, 1986 Aug 18; 23.3 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - 4-17; Tape 1 of 1 by AJ, 1986 Aug 18; 23.4 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - 4-19; Tape 1 of 1 by AJ, 1986 Aug 18; 23.5 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - 4-20, 23.6 (Box 23, Item 6)
  - 4-21, 23.7 (Box 23, Item 7)
  - 4-18; Archive 335, 1978 Mar 1; 23.8 (Box 23, Item 8)
  - 4-19; Archive 337, 1978 Mar 9; 23.9 (Box 23, Item 9)
  - 4-20; Archive 339, 24.1 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - 4-21; Archive 341, 24.2 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - 4-23; Archive 345A, 24.3 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - 4-24; Archive 347; Tape 1 of 1, 1978 May 4; 24.4 (Box 24, Item 4)
  - 4-25; Archive 349; Time: 23:00, 1978 May 17; 24.5 (Box 24, Item 5)
  - 4-26; Archive 351; Tape 1 of 1, 1978 May 25; 24.6 (Box 24, Item 6)
  - 4-24; Archive 353, 1978 Jun 3; 24.7 (Box 24, Item 7)
  - 4-28; Archive 355, 1978 Jun; 24.8 (Box 24, Item 8)
  - 4-29; Archive 357, 24.9 (Box 24, Item 9)
  - 4-30; Archive 359, 25.1 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - 4-31; Archive 361, 25.2 (Box 25, Item 2)
  - 4-32; Archive 363 (Copy of 364), 25.3 (Box 25, Item 3)
  - 4-33; Archive 365, 25.4 (Box 25, Item 4)
  - 4-34; Archive 367, 25.5 (Box 25, Item 5)
  - 4-35; Archive 369, 1978 Aug 4; 25.6 (Box 25, Item 6)
  - 4-36; Archive 371, 1978 Aug 8; 25.7 (Box 25, Item 7)
  - 4-37; Archive 373, 25.8 (Box 25, Item 8)
  - 4-38; Archive 375, 1978 Aug 23; 25.9 (Box 25, Item 9)
  - 4-39; Archive 377, 1978 Sept 2; 25.10 (Box 25, Item 10)
  - 3-10; Sequence A; Tape 2 and 12, 1980 Jul 27; 26.1 (Box 26, Item 1)
  - 3-32, 1989 Nov 5; 26.2 (Box 26, Item 2)
  - 3-34, 26.3 (Box 26, Item 3)
  - 3-36; Tape 2 of 2; 1st inode: 32,982, 1989 Nov 5; 26.4 (Box 26, Item 4)
  - 3-37, 26.5 (Box 26, Item 5)
  - 3-38, 26.6 (Box 26, Item 6)
  - 3-39; Tape 3 of 6 by FLC; 1st inode: 80,377, 1989 Nov 5; 26.7 (Box 26, Item 7)
  - 3-40; Tape 4 of 6 by FLC; 1st inode: 119116, 1989 Nov 5; 26.8 (Box 26, Item 8)
  - 3-41, 1989 Nov 5; 26.9 (Box 26, Item 9)
  - [3-9]; Sequence A; Tape 1 of 12, 1980 Jul 27; 27.1 (Box 27, Item 1)
  - [3-11]; Sequence A; Tape 3 of 12, 1980 Jul 27; 27.2 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - 7-39; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 12; Tape 12 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.3 (Box 27, Item 3)
  - 7-40; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 11; Tape 11 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.4 (Box 27, Item 4)
  - 7-41; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 10; Tape 10 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.5 (Box 27, Item 5)
  - 7-42; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 9; Tape 9 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.6 (Box 27, Item 6)
  - 7-43; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 8; Tape 8 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.7 (Box 27, Item 7)
  - 7-44; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 7; Tape 7 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.8 (Box 27, Item 8)
  - 7-45; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 6; Tape 6 of 14; Time: 0930, 1975 Jan 26; 27.9 (Box 27, Item 9)
  - 7-46; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 5; Tape 5 of 14, 1975 Jan 26; 27.10 (Box 27, Item 10)
  - 7-48; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 3; Tape 3 of 14; Time: 09:30, 1975 Jan 26; 28.1 (Box 28, Item 1)
  - [7-38]; FULLDUMPF; Sequence 13; Tape 13 of 14; Time: 09:30, 1975 Jan 26; 28.2 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - Archive 259, 1977 May 18; 28.3 (Box 28, Item 3)
  - Archive 159B, 1977 May 19; 28.4 (Box 28, Item 4)
  - 4-1, 28.5 (Box 28, Item 5)
  - 4-2, 28.6 (Box 28, Item 6)
  - 4-4, 28.7 (Box 28, Item 7)
  - 4-5, 1989 Jan 16; 28.8 (Box 28, Item 8)
  - 4-18; Tape 1 of 1 by AJ, 1986 Aug 18; 28.9 (Box 28, Item 9)
  - 4-22; Tape 2 of 4 by AJ; 1st inode: 17188, 1986 Aug 30; 29.1 (Box 29, Item 1)
  - 4-23; Tape 3 of 4 by AJ; 1st inode: 37079, 1986 Aug 30; 29.2 (Box 29, Item 2)
  - 4-23; Tape 4 of 4 by AJ; 1st inode: 52332, 1986 Aug 30; 29.3 (Box 29, Item 3)
  - 4-24, 29.4 (Box 29, Item 4)
  - 4-25, 29.5 (Box 29, Item 5)
  - 4-25; Tape 1 of 8 by AJ, 1986 Aug 30; 29.6 (Box 29, Item 6)
  - 4-26; Tape 2 of 8 by AJ; 1st inode: 6711, 1986 Aug 30; 29.7 (Box 29, Item 7)
  - 4-27, 1986 Aug 30; 29.8 (Box 29, Item 8)
  - 4-28, 1986 Aug 30; 29.9 (Box 29, Item 9)
  - 4-29; Tape 5 of 8 by AJ; 1st inode: 27694, 1986 Aug 30; 29.10 (Box 29, Item 10)
  - 4-30; Tape 6 of 8 by AJ; Ist inode: 34046, 1986 Aug 30; 30.1 (Box 30, Item 1)
  - [4-31]; Tape 7 of 8 by AJ; 1st inode: 41117, 1986 Aug 30; 30.2 (Box 30, Item 2)
  - 4-32; Tape 8 of 8 by AJ; 1st inode: 47754, 1986 Aug 31; 30.3 (Box 30, Item 3)
  - 4-33; Tape 1 of 2 by AJ, 1986 Aug 31; 30.4 (Box 30, Item 4)
  - 4-34; [Tape 2 of 2], 1986 Aug 31; 30.5 (Box 30, Item 5)
  - Unlabeled, 30.6 (Box 30, Item 6)
  - Unlabeled, 30.7 (Box 30, Item 7)
  - Mini Age Master Distribution Tape; Tops-20 Dumper Format; Tape 1 of 1, 1984 Jul 3; 30.8 (Box 30, Item 8)
  - UNIX 4.1 Age; R. Bates; 1600 BPI; Blocking 20; USC/ISI, 1984 Mar 20; 30.9 (Box 30, Item 9)
  - Master Age Distribtution Tape; Tops 20 Dumper, 1983 Nov 1; 30.10 (Box 30, Item 10)
  - Unlabeled, 31.1-31.10 (Box 31, Item 1-10)
  - VMS Age; R. Bates; USC/ISI, 1984 Mar 9; 32.1 (Box 32)
  - A/I Handbook; Volumes I, II, III; Fixed Block Unlabeled; EBCDIC Format; 132 Chars/Record - 10 Records/Block 1600 BPI, 32.2 (Box 32)
  - Sequence A; Tape 4, 1981 Jan 25; 32.3 (Box 32, Item 3)
  - Sequence A; Tape 5, 32.4 (Box 32, Item 4)
  - Sequence A; Tape 6, 32.5 (Box 32, Item 5)
  - Sequence A; Tape 7, 1981 Jan 25; 32.6 (Box 32, Item 6)
  - Sequence A; Tape 8, 1981 Jan 25; 32.7 (Box 32, Item 7)
  - Sequence A; Tape 9, 32.8 (Box 32, Item 8)
  - Sequence A; Tape 10, 32.9 (Box 32, Item 9)
  - Sequence A; Tape 11, 1981 Jan 25; 32.10 (Box 32, Item 10)
  - Sequence B; Tape 1, 1981 Jan 25; 33.1 (Box 33, Item 1)
  - Sequence B; Tape 2, 1981 Jan 25; 33.2 (Box 33, Item 2)
  - Sequence B; Tape 3, 1981 Jan 25; 33.3 (Box 33, Item 3)
  - Sequence B; Tape 4, 1981 Jan 25; 33.4 (Box 33, Item 4)
  - Sequence B; Tape 5, 1981 Jan 25; 33.5 (Box 33, Item 5)
  - Sequence B; Tape 6, 1981 Jan 25; 33.6 (Box 33, Item 6)
  - Sequence B; Tape 7, 1981 Jan 25; 33.7 (Box 33, Item 7)
  - Sequence B; Tape 8, 1981 Jan 25; 33.8 (Box 33, Item 8)
  - Sequence B; Tape 9, 1981 Jan 25; 33.9 (Box 33, Item 9)
  - Sequence B; Tape 10, 1981 Jan 25; 34.1 (Box 34, Item 1)
  - Sequence B; Tape 11, 1981 Jan 25; 34.2 (Box 34, Item 2)
  - Sequence A; Tape 1, 1981 Jan 25; 34.3 (Box 34, Item 3)
  - Sequence A; Tape 2, 1981 Jan 25; 34.4 (Box 34, Item 4)
  - Sequence A; Tape 3, 1981 Jan 25; 34.5 (Box 34, Item 5)
  - Sequence A; Tape 12, 1981 Jan 25; 34.6 (Box 34, Item 6)
  - Sequence A; Tape 13 of 13, 1981 Jan 25; 34.7 (Box 34, Item 7)
  - Archive A1007, 34.8 (Box 34, Item 8)
  - Archive A1011 by Burgess, 1983 May 9; 34.9 (Box 34, Item 9)
  - A1013 by Burgess; Tape 1 of 1, 1983 May 22; 35.1 (Box 35, Item 1)
  - Archive A1015 by MLS; Tape 1 of 1, 1983 May 26; 35.2 (Box 35, Item 2)
  - Archive A1017 by Operator Sike, 1983 Jun 8; 35.3 (Box 35, Item 3)
  - Archive A1019 by SE, 1983 Jun 16; 35.4 (Box 35, Item 4)
  - Archive A1027 by SE, 1983 Aug 16; 35.5 (Box 35, Item 5)
  - Archive A1029 by SE, 1983 Aug 19; 35.6 (Box 35, Item 6)
  - Archive A1031 by SE, 1983 Sept 7; 35.7 (Box 35, Item 7)
  - 2-18, 35.8 (Box 35, Item 8)
  - 3-18, 1989 Oct 8; 35.9 (Box 35, Item 9)
  - 3-19; Quarterly Level 0; Tape 1 of 2 by Fh, 1989 Oct 8; 36.1 (Box 36, Item 1)
  - 3-20, 36.2 (Box 36, Item 2)
  - 3-21, 1989 Oct 8; 36.3 (Box 36, Item 3)
  - 3-22; Quarterly Level 0; Tape 2 of 2 by Fh; 1st inode: 41088, 1989 Oct 8; 36.4 (Box 36, Item 4)
  - 3-23, 36.5 (Box 36, Item 5)
  - 3-24; Quarterly Level 0; Tape 2 of 2; 1st inode: 32997, 1989 Oct 8; 36.6 (Box 36, Item 6)
  - 3-25, 1989 Oct 8; 36.7 (Box 36, Item 7)
  - 3-26, 36.8 (Box 36, Item 8)
  - 3-27; Quarterly Level 0; Tape 3 of 5 by Fh; 1st inode: 78227, 1989 Oct 8; 36.9 (Box 36, Item 9)
  - 3-28, 1989 Oct 8; 37.1 (Box 37, Item 1)
  - 3-29, 37.2 (Box 37, Item 2)
  - 3-31, 37.3 (Box 37, Item 3)
  - 4-3, 37.4 (Box 37, Item 4)
  - 4-4; 2020 Full Dump, 1987 Oct 12; 37.5 (Box 37, Item 5)
  - 4-5, 37.6 (Box 37, Item 6)
  - 4-9, 37.7 (Box 37, Item 7)
  - 4-11, 37.8 (Box 37, Item 8)
  - 4-12, 37.9 (Box 37, Item 9)
  - 2-50, 1989 Aug 21; 38.1 (Box 38, Item 1)
  - Floor 21, 38.2 (Box 38, Item 2)
  - Blue 2 1-11; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1 by WS, 1989 Feb 22; 38.3 (Box 38, Item 3)
  - [Blue 2 1-12], 38.4 (Box 38, Item 4)
  - Blue 2 1-13, 38.5 (Box 38, Item 5)
  - Blue 2 1-14; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1 by WS, 1989 Mar 8; 38.6 (Box 38, Item 6)
  - Blue 2 1-15; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1 by WS, 1989 Mar 6; 38.7 (Box 38, Item 7)
  - Blue 2 1-16, 38.8 (Box 38, Item 8)
  - Blue 2 1-17; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1 by WS, 1989 Mar 17; 38.9 (Box 38, Item 9)
  - Blue 2 1-18, 39.1 (Box 39, Item 1)
  - Blue 2 1-19; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1, 1989 Mar 24; 39.2 (Box 39, Item 2)
  - [Blue 2 1-20], 39.3 (Box 39, Item 3)
  - Blue 2 1-21; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1, 1989 Mar 31; 39.4 (Box 39, Item 4)
  - Blue 2 1-22, 39.5 (Box 39, Item 5)
  - Blue 2 1-23; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1, 1989 Apr 17; 39.6 (Box 39, Item 6)
  - Blue 2 1-24; Specification: Incremental Dump; Tape 1 of 1, 1989 Apr 20; 39.7 (Box 39, Item 7)
  - Blue 2 1-25, 39.8 (Box 39, Item 8)
  - Blue 2 1-26, 39.9 (Box 39, Item 9)
  - Blue 2 1-32, 40.1 (Box 40, Item 1)
  - Blue 2 1-33, 1989 Feb 21; 40.2 (Box 40, Item 2)
  - Blue 2 1-35, 1989 Mar 13; 40.3 (Box 40, Item 3)
  - Blue 2 2-2, 40.4 (Box 40, Item 4)
  - Blue 2 2-3, 40.5 (Box 40, Item 5)
  - 1d #8, 1988 Jul 31; 40.6 (Box 40, Item 6)
  - Unlabeled, 1989 Feb 27; 40.7 (Box 40, Item 7)
  - Blue 4 3-13, 40.8 (Box 40, Item 8)
  - BCPL BH(101) University of Essex; Backup/Interchange/gtk, 40.9 (Box 40, Item 9)
  - 1-42; Archive 684, 1981 Apr 14; 41.1 (Box 41, Item 1)
  - 1-43; Archive 686, 1981 Apr 19; 41.2 (Box 41, Item 2)
  - 1-44; Archive 688, 1981 Apr 23; 41.3 (Box 41, Item 3)
  - 1-45; Archive 690 (copy of 689), 1981 Aug 3; 41.4 (Box 41, Item 4)
  - 1-46; Archive 692, 1981 Apr 30; 41.5 (Box 41, Item 5)
  - 1-47; Archive 694, 1981 May 7; 41.6 (Box 41, Item 6)
  - 1-48; Archive 696, 1981 May 11; 41.7 (Box 41, Item 7)
  - 1-49; Archive 698, 1981 May 15; 41.8 (Box 41, Item 8)
  - 2-1; Archive 700; Time: 21:16, 1981 May 20; 42.1 (Box 42, Item 1)
  - 2-2; Archive 702; Time: 9:10, 1981 May 26; 42.2 (Box 42, Item 2)
  - 2-3; Archive 704 (copy 703), 1981 Jun 2; 42.3 (Box 42, Item 3)
  - 2-4; Archive 706, 1981 Jun 3; 42.4 (Box 42, Item 4)
  - 4-5; Archive 708, 1981 Jun 4; 42.5 (Box 42, Item 5)
  - 2-6; Archive 710, 1981 Jun 7; 42.6 (Box 42, Item 6)
  - 2-7; Archive 712, 1981 Jun 11; 42.7 (Box 42, Item 7)
  - 2-8; Archive 714, 1981 Jun 15; 42.8 (Box 42, Item 8)
  - 2-9; Archive 716, 1981 Jun 16; 42.9 (Box 42, Item 9)
  - 2-10; Archive 718, 1981 Jun 21; 42.10 (Box 42, Item 10)
  - 2-11; Archive 720, 1981 Jun 22; 43.1 (Box 43, Item 1)
  - 2-12; Archive 722, 1981 Jun 28; 43.2 (Box 43, Item 2)
  - 2-13; Archive 724, 1981 Jul 5; 43.3 (Box 43, Item 3)
  - Archive 184 (copied), 1982 Dec 27; 43.4 (Box 43, Item 4)
  - Archive 188 (copied), 1982 Dec 27; 43.5 (Box 43, Item 5)
  - Archive 188 (copied), 1982 Dec 27; 43.6 (Box 43, Item 6)
  - Archive 190 (copied), 1982 Dec 27; 43.7 (Box 43, Item 7)
  - Archive 192 (copied), 1982 Dec 27; 43.8 (Box 43, Item 8)
  - Archive 194 (copied), 1982 Dec 27; 43.9 (Box 43, Item 9)
  - Archive 196 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 43.10 (Box 43, Item 10)
  - Archive 198 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.1 (Box 44, Item 1)
  - Archive 200 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.2 (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Archive 202 (copied), 1982 Dec 23; 44.3 (Box 44, Item 3)